[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the four Galilean moons of Jupiter is noted as the most volcanically active body in the solar system?", "correct_answer": "Io", "incorrect_answers": ["Europa", "Callisto", "Ganymede"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would speak Hindi as their first language?", "correct_answer": "101", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "21", "463"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Valtrex (valacyclovir) treats which one of the following conditions?", "correct_answer": "Genital herpes", "incorrect_answers": ["Pityriasis alba", "HPV (genital warts)", "Syphilis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tina Fey, who adapted the script for Mean Girls from the book Queen Bees and Wannabees, used to be head writer for which TV show?", "correct_answer": "Saturday Night Live", "incorrect_answers": ["Mad TV", "Spin City", "That 70s Show"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This ancient Greek philosopher, who taught Alexander the Great, wrote a book on zoology entitled History of Animals.", "correct_answer": "Aristotle", "incorrect_answers": ["Plato", "Socrates", "Democritus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What large mountain range is located entirely within the territory of Italy?", "correct_answer": "Apennines", "incorrect_answers": ["Alps", "Andes", "Carpathians"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Austin, Texas is called The Live Music Capital of the World.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the American states below does not have part of the Yellow Stone National Park in it?", "correct_answer": "Utah", "incorrect_answers": ["Wyoming", "Montana", "Idaho"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did the action in the movie House of 1000 Corpses start on the night before Halloween of 1977?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Johann Regiomontanus first introduced the plus sign, + , in this year.", "correct_answer": "1456", "incorrect_answers": ["1656", "1556", "1756"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a shaker, mix 1 oz Kahlua, 1 oz butterscotch schnapps and 6 oz milk. Strain into a glass.", "correct_answer": "Kahlua Butterball", "incorrect_answers": ["Irish Coffee", "John Collins", "Hot Toddy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the fourth estate?", "correct_answer": "the press", "incorrect_answers": ["the clergy", "the nobles", "the commoners"]}]